Sherzod Qodirov Fronted Developer(React js)

Telegram: @Qodirov_Sherzod React JS, a user interface developed using Flux for SPA. -React-Router was used to turn the application into a one-page application. - React worked with JS components, shapes, events, switches, routers, animations and the Flux concept. -Introduced the latest js (ES6) functions to improve code standards and stability.



sherzodqadirov01@gmail.com

+998994236134

Tashkent, Uzbekistan

...

linkedin.com/in/sherzod-qodirov

-

github.com/sherzodqodirov/Portfolio

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering

Tashkent University of information Technologies

09/2020 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

React developer

isystem academy

03/2022 - 04/2022

Freelancer

React developer

04/2022 - Present

Portfolio

link to portfolio 🗷

SKILLS

HTML CSS

S SASS(SCSS)

Boostrap

JavaScript

React.js(Hooks, Router, Redux, Redux-toolkit)

Unit tests (React JS)

Git

Axios/fetch

CERTIFICATES

Frontend Developer (03/2022 - Present)

link: https://i.ibb.co/PMzrX22/certificate.jpg

LANGUAGES

uzb

Native or Bilingual Proficiency ru

Full Professional Proficiency

eng

Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

Travel

Volunteering, community service or charity

Sports such as team or league competition, hiking, or other exercise

Creativity, including writing and music